Destiny. Fate. Dreams.
These unstoppable ideals are
held deep in the heart of man.
As long as there are people
who seek freedom in this life,
these things shall not
vanish from the earth.
People tell me my head's in the clouds.
I don't care what they say
because I'm dreaming of you.
You are the treasure I found.
So bright, so bold, it's so elusive.
It's hard to look away.
Even though it's blinding me.
There are no words to
describe how I feel inside.
I'm really, really stuck on you, oh, oh.
I have to follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
And I won't stop till I
get there, you will see.
You're all I need to have
the strength to believe.
Believe in wonderland.
I'm gonna follow my dreams,
however crazy they seem.
I'm gonna share them
with you, a love so true.
You're all I want,
together we can move on.
Live how we want to.
There is no limit to us,
we have the power of love.
So we don't wanna live ordinary lives.
We have a chance to live in paradise.
We believe in one another.
We've got trouble!
Vivi, where are they?
Oh, Igaram, what is it?
Luffy and all the others.
Where are they?
The sea.
They are pirates.
Oh, no.
Listen up, you guys.
Pirates are nothing but scum.
Every one of them.
Hey, wait.
Don't you remember?
What are you saying? Come on.
You used to be one. You're right!
How could I forget? Ah-ha!
Oh, baby! Let's dance!
Ah, yeah! Dance! Dance!
That's right!
In the fucking style!
We're all on our way back!
It looks like those two
subdued the enemy ship.
It took them long enough.
Don't tell me.
They're dancing, right?
I trusted those two to finish off that
pirate ship that tried to escape us,
and this is what they do.
Disappointed.
Hina's disappointed.
Have you finished deploying all the ships?
Yes, that's affirmative, ma 'am.
Every harbor in this dust bowl
of the country is now blockaded.
But, ma 'am, there's one thing
I'm concerned about. What's that?
Well, it's just the
Straw Hatch ship, ma 'am.
It was confirmed to be near
Aramalu, and now it's gone.
Don't tell me they've
left the country already.
No, I doubt that, ma 'am.
Then go search for it.
Scour the entire coast.
Yes, right away.
Oh, no.
Miss Hina, we're sorry it took us so long.
Aren't you gonna ask
us why it took so long?
Why'd it take so long?
Because we were picking these
flowers for you, Miss Hina.
No, thanks.
Now, man your positions right away.
We're going after the Straw Hat Pirates.
The Straw Hats?
Not bad.
So, a final farewell,
old kingdom of the sand.
Lupi, aren't you full yet?
These Alabasta dishes are
great, aren't they, Sanji?
You should make them sometime.
Yeah, I like them too, so I got
some recipes from terracotta.
I also got some of their local spices.
Um, what's wrong, Nami? Are you sick?
I'll give you a piece of this if
you want, but just a small one.
Nami, if you're thinking about
Vivi again, I understand.
Listen, moping around about it won't help.
I know it must be really hard for you.
You two got close.
Just keep your chin up, okay?
That's not bad.
I'm just sad we didn't take the reward.
The one billion berries.
You're moping about the money?!
Usopp fell off!
You shouldn't mislead
people like that, Nami!
What did you think I was upset about?
We just walked away from a huge
payday that we actually earned!
Usopp fell down!
That's his problem!
But you caused it!
Conney, wake up! You're needed!
It's no use, Igaram.
But the world government has
released new bounties on their heads!
We should at least warn them.
I had the duck squadron take them.
Even if Karoo could catch up to
them, it wouldn't change anything.
Why's that?
Those new bounties, they'll
actually make them happy?
They'll all be tickled pink!
But princess, they...
Trust me, they'll be fine.
Now out you go!
I've got to get some rest.
I've got a big day tomorrow, remember?
Oh that's right Your coming of age
ceremony is tomorrow morning at ten.
Uh-huh.
Now, come on, Karoo.
Let's get some sleep.
Something's bothering me. Hey!
She's awfully calm.
Strange.
Very strange.
It's really quiet, isn't it, Karoo?
We haven't had a night
this quiet in a long time.
The cook who guards the refrigerator
from a late-night raider is gone.
So too is the swordsman
who trains every night.
The navigator who throws
pillows when she's asleep.
Or two, they're gone.
Snail communication? From who? Don't know.
He called himself Bon.
Just Bon? That's it?
Uh, never heard of the guy.
That's strange.
He insists that you're all good friends.
Friends with us?
Hello?
Hey, old friends, it's me!
I bet you never thought you'd
hear from me again, didn't you?
You freak! Shut up!
So you escaped Mr.
Two, and what do you want?
Straw Hat!
I'd recognize that force anywhere!
You're right, I escaped.
And I want to keep it that
way, so don't call me Mr.
Two.
If the Marines intercept this call,
they'll be able to ascertain the
locations of both me and you.
Thanks a lot, you jerk!
Tell us what you want.
Oh, it's not what I want.
It's what I have! Your ship! Stop joking!
I'm gonna kick your butt for saying that!
Where are you?
On your ship, the Going Merry!
I should have kicked him harder.
Hey! Call down!
Please!
I mean, we are friends, right? Right!
He's at the upper part
of the Sandora River.
Can we trust him?
We did become friends
that one time, but...
That was before we knew he
was part of Baroque Works.
I guess we have no choice. You're right.
He has our ship.
If he tries to trick us, I'll be more than
happy to kick the crap out of him again.
All right, we gotta move.
Hey, you guys.
I, uh, I don't...
I don't know what to do.
If you were me, what would you do?
VV, we can give you 12
hours to make a decision.
We'll travel down the Sandora,
after teaching Ballerina Boy
why he shouldn't steal from us,
and by noon tomorrow, we'll
draw near the Eastern Harbor.
I doubt we'll be able
to drop anchor, though.
If you do decide to join us,
that's going to be the only
chance for you to come aboard.
Twelve o 'clock on the dot.
It's your choice.
You could stay a princess
or become a pirate.
I'm sure being a pirate doesn't
compare to being a princess,
but we'd sure love to have you.
Yeah, so why wait?
Come with us now, Vivi!
Knock it off, Luffy.
Yeah, come on. Why?
Don't you guys want her to join us?
We do, but that's something
she has to decide for herself.
Twelve o 'clock on the dot.
If it's the eastern harbor, it'll
take four hours to get there on Karoo.
If I left here by eight,
I'd make it on time.
Life is a pirate, huh?
Adventures on the high seas,
surrounded by loyal friends?
If I miss this chance,
I know I'll never get another one
like it for the rest of my life.
On the other hand, I have
duties here as a princess,
and at a critical time since this
land's in the midst of a rebirth.
Whatever I do choose, you'll
stay with me, won't you?
Say, Karoo, what would you like to do?
Finally!
Long time no see, my friends!
Did you guys miss little old me?
Not a bit.
Let's unload. Later, ducks.
Thanks for the lift.
Yeah, you ducks take care of yourselves!
Have a safe trip.
Say bye to the king, the old tube-haired
guy, and all the others for us!
Come on, fellas!
Farewell!
May you ugly ducklings
turn into beautiful swans!
Wait! Hold on! Yeah, what?
Don't dare want me!
That's just rude!
You should learn some manners, pretty boy!
Friends aren't supposed to
talk to their friends that way!
Quit saying that, you weirdo!
We're not friends, we're enemies!
You lied to us!
No, I didn't!
I just didn't mention that I
was a member of Baroque Works!
Besides, none of that
really matters now, does it?
Baroque works is done for now.
And that means that
we're no longer enemies.
Hey, move it.
Oh, my bad.
Well, if we're not enemies, ballerina guy,
then why the heck did you steal our ship?
Oh, how dumb are you? Watch it! Listen!
If I hadn't taken your little
ship from where it was moored,
what do you think would
have happened to it?
The Marines probably would have seized it.
Change that probably
to indefinitely, honey.
The Marines have been looking all
over for you guys and your ship.
Every port in the
country's been blockaded!
Loguetown!
Hey, hold on.
Are you telling us you took the
Going Mary so the Marines wouldn't?
Really? How come?
Cause you guys are my friends!
Oh, give me a break, guys!
We may have had to fight
on opposite sides of a war,
but our friendship will
last all of your turns!
Need help loading?
Nope, this is the last
one. Friends? Yeah, right.
Tell the truth, Twinkle Toes.
You and your crew don't have a chance
of getting through that blockade.
But you might, if you had us as allies.
Yeah! Like me!
That's right, you got me.
But in trying times such as these,
we have to band together
under the flag of friendship.
If you believe in true
friendship, say aye! Aye!
Aye!
Straw Hats!
Where are you guys?
Miss Hina, we've spotted
the Straw Hat ship.
It's near the upper reaches
of the Sandora River.
What do you think we should do, Captain?
Attack, of course.
Igaram, I will!
I will be Queen of the Pirates! SCREAM!
Baby!
Oh, good morning, Igaram.
What's the matter?
You're sweating. Enough!
Where are your manners?
You can't just barge in here.
The princess needs her privacy.
Now go!
Please forgive me.
I just wanted to say good morning.
Is that all?
No, I mean, yes.
Quit blabbering!
What are you still doing here?
I told you to get out!
I guess it was my imagination.
Huh?
Oh, your majesty.
I didn't see you there.
Good morning.
Yes, good morning.
You too, huh?
Terracotta can be quite scary.
What did you do?
Try to say hello?
I don't know.
Terracotta, isn't this too tight?
This is how formal attire is
supposed to fit upon a princess.
I heard that the square
is already full of people.
Really?
When it was announced that your
speech would begin promptly at ten,
everyone started getting anxious.
No one wants to miss a word.
Your coming-of-age ceremony should have
been held two years ago
when you were fourteen.
Since it was delayed so long,
it's made the people even more
excited for this special event.
But I don't have any pressing
information to share with them.
They're coming because they love you.
You don't have to say one word.
All you do is show up and let
everyone see how much you've grown.
The Coming of Age ceremony is held
to celebrate you becoming an adult.
It's not about speeches,
and you should be mindful of the king's
feelings in taking the time for it.
Oh, yeah.
I heard your speech today is
going to be broadcast throughout
all of Alabasta with transponder
snails and amplifiers.
How exciting!
I'm really looking forward to it.
I received a report that a battle
broke out at the harbor. I see.
In light of this, you realize
we can no longer get involved.
Fire! Fire!
Damn it!
Shoot cannonballs!
I can't deflect pointy things!
Seriously, give me a break!
If we take any more iron spears
to the bottom of the ship,
it'll just be a matter
of time before we sink.
More!
Hey, I can't keep putting
these holes, you guys!
Don't just stand there and do something!
What more can we do?
It takes all our effort
to protect one side!
One ship versus eight isn't a fair fight!
If this was hand-to-hand combat,
we'd have a better chance.
We're stuck.
Whether we chase them or run away,
they won't change their formation.
The Black Spear Formation.
It's a work of art.
It's the Black Cage Unit Specially!
Idiots!
Hey, hypnotist!
I thought you were a pirate! I am!
Now why don't you shut up?
My reasons are my own.
Where do I know that guy from?
It took a long time,
but I finally found him.
That annoying, crazy cook and
his gang of violent cutthroats.
Here, today, I vow to sink him.
Stare at this ream.
You're about to help me finally
prove that I'm not a weirdo.
In fact, my services alone
will pave the way to victory.
One, two.
Oh!
Brother!
Whoa!
Usopp, did you do that?
Amazing!
Yes, just as I calculated.
It was me!
That's what happens to enemy
ships when I'm on the job!
Yeah!
That was amazing, Nosy!
The ships in the south have all sunk.
Now nothing can prevent
us from breaking through!
Oh!
Buncle!
We got trouble. What's wrong?
Black Cage!
What's going on?
Black Cage, Hina!
She's a marine captain.
We're in her jurisdiction.
She's a real pain.
We need to hurry up and fly the coop.
Yes, sir, Mr. Bon Clay, sir.
Seems we've weakened them quite a bit.
There's no ship we can't take down
using our Black Cage formation.
Don't get too confident.
Underestimating criminals such as these
can come at the expense of one's own life.
now remember once we
arrive you guys are to
stay back or you might
get in my way and then
Hina would be annoyed yes ma 'am you guys
need to wake up we have
to run if we can pass
through that point in
the south we can escape
but if we don't change course immediately
they'll take us down for
sure if you want to go
go we can't go that way
and exactly why not Mr.
Bon Clay we Need to set sail while we still
can there's no more time sir noon at the
Eastern Harbor we've got An appointment
there's no time to go
around we'll go straight
through what Suicide
it's ludicrous is there
some treasure you're not
telling me about This
we're throwing away
your lives fine run off
and die we have to go
get one Of our friends
So, it's for your pal
that you risk it all.
Vivi, I'm coming in, okay?
Sure, the door's open.
Sweetie, what did you want to talk?
Phoebe, amazing.
I mistook you for the queen and her youth.
Uncanny resemblance and just as beautiful.
A vision of elegance.
Have a seat, Daddy.
No.
Father, Igaron. Hmm?
I have an important matter to discuss.
Great Bon Clay!
Running now would go against
everything Bon Clay stands for.
If we abandon allies who are risking
their lives to pick up a friend,
could we live with ourselves tomorrow?
Listen, guys.
Straw Hats, too.
What I must say is of great importance.
Miss Hina, the enemy
ships are splitting up.
The duck ship is headed south.
The duck is probably meant as a decoy.
Well,
actually, it appears the entire Strawhead
crew is on board the duck ship, Captain.
It's the sheep ship
they're using as the decoy.
Follow the duck.
Return to formation immediately.
Three minutes.
Prepare to attack. Ready?
Full speed ahead!
So tell me something.
I am the Straw Hat you idiots
are looking for, right?
Oh, Emma!
Miss Hina, the sheep ship
is heading east. What?
You must be feeling pretty stupid right
now falling for such a simple trick.
See, we're masters of disguise.
as well as friends to the Straw Hat.
Even if I stray from my code as a man?
Even if I stray from my code as a woman?
I could never betray my basic humanity.
That is the difference between us.
If my brethren and I are to
fall, we will fall together?
clinging to our freedom
and watching its bloom.
By Bunkley.
Bring it on, sister.
Hina's humiliated.
Whoop!
Buckley!
Huh?
I promise you, Vaughn Blaine,
we will never forget you!
If we are to fall, let it be in the sea.
The flower of friendship is rejoicing.
We don't know who the ringleader is.
Right?
It's an underground organization.
Even its members know absolutely nothing
about the identity of their boss.
So this country's enemy has no name.
It's impossible for us to gather
information on them from the outside.
Further investigation might
put the country at risk.
But we do have a lead.
Isn't that correct? Yes.
Igaram, do you know what
I'm thinking right now?
No, no, I don't! Leave me be!
I have to go back to my
work! Igaram! No! Stop it!
This isn't a game!
All the more reason to be honest with me!
I can't sit around and do nothing!
Ah!
They're after us again!
Get out of our way!
Look!
There she is!
It's Vivi!
Princess Vivi, you're a vision!
We love you!
Princess!
She's all grown up! Princess!
Then, Vivi, let me ask
you just one question.
It all started on that day.
Are you prepared to live at all cost?
I went on a little adventure.
Princess Vivi's speech has started.
Hurry up!
I've been waiting so long!
Oh, it's so exciting!
The ceremony in Alabana
has finally started.
That was delayed by two hours.
What happened?
Ah, well.
I can only hope it
won't cause a commotion.
Come and listen, Koza!
Hey, come on!
Phoebe's speech has already started!
The amplifiers are cranked all the way up.
I could be underground
and still hear every word.
A journey to cross the Dark Sea, but
what I found was a grand adventure.
The sheer vastness of the
ocean was overwhelming,
and yet it brought me to a series
of islands so unbelievable.
They defied imagination.
With such wondrous environments,
inhabited by strange creatures.
At times, the melody of the waves was
quiet, swaying gently as if easing my soul.
And there were other times, when the
melody was violently laughing at me,
as if threatening to rip
my very heart in two.
In that dark, dark storm, I
encountered a single, small ship.
The ship spoke to me
while pushing me onward.
It said with a clear, singular
voice, Can't you see the light?
This wondrous ship,
which never strayed off course
even through pitch-black darkness,
danced its way across the huge waves.
The mighty ship kept its
stem pointed straight ahead,
thwarting every obstacle
the ocean could throw at.
Finally, as the ship roused my spirits,
it said, Look, there is a light.
History will one day catalogue
this experience as an illusion,
but I will always remember
it as a singular truth.
What's she talking about?
The secret battle she fought
against that group of criminals.
And...
Vivi!
Forget about it.
You heard the speech.
That was Vivi's voice without a doubt.
They're just broadcasting the ceremony
that's being held in Alubarna.
Vivi's already made up
her mind not to come here.
No, I don't buy it.
I say she's here.
This is the Tamarisk place, right?
Yeah, that's it. Let's go. It's past noon.
There's no way she wouldn't have come.
She's definitely here.
Let's get out and look for her.
This is bad, guys.
The Marines are after us again.
Exactly how many ships are out there?
I see at least six.
Damn it, let's move.
Give it up, Luffy.
Vivi's course is on a road
far different from ours.
Let me know what's going on, Vivi.
What the hell is going on?
Hey, show your face!
We know you're a fake!
It's Squad Captain Igaram!
Where's the real Vivi?
We heard her voice, so where the
hell is the princess sneaking from?
At least Vivi is safe.
Everyone!
Vivi!
Karoo!
See, she came! Silver!
We need to go back!
Better hurry!
The Marines are right behind us, too!
I came to say goodbye!
What'd she say?
Karoo, handset.
Sorry but I can't go with you.
Thank you so much for everything!
Who's the princess talking to?
No way.
I think I just spotted princess Vivi.
She's supposed to be at
the ceremony in Alubarna.
I'd like to go on more adventures.
But I can't ignore the needs of my
country which I love more than anything.
Where is Vivi?
We want our princess, not a
captain in disguise! Hey, princess!
You need a shade!
Ma-ma-ma!
Nice dancing, he girl!
Yeah, keep it up!
Everyone can tell those aren't real!
I have to stay.
I hope you understand.
I see.
Thank you.
Our sign needs to be an X.
How come? We're pirates!
You know that it's literal translation
means death to one's opponents, right?
That's fine.
It must be an X.
It looks cool. Covey.
Yeah, I like it.
It doesn't matter what it is.
That's not the point.
Just write it.
I will.
I...
this will do.
I will remain here and fulfill my duty.
It's a sign of our friendship.
If we ever meet again?
No matter how much time's passed!
will you still call me friend?
Did you hear that?
The princess has some kind
of bond with the Straw Hacks.
Yeah.
Princess Vivi considers
those pirates friends?
You forever idiot!
Don't reply, got it?
The Marines now know about Vivi and us.
If they can prove she has a
connection to us, it's all over.
She'll be considered a criminal.
Turn away, not another word.
No matter what happens
on that island, remember,
this thing on all our arms
is a sign of our friendship.
Ah!
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for!
One piece.